

FULL STACK DEVELOPER | PUBLIC RELATIONS

☑ jackpowis@gmail.com **③** jackgay.herokuapp.com/ **⑤** + 447969068949 **♀** New York, NY **in** jack-gay/ **۞** j4ckp0w15g4y

SUMMARY

I am an experienced and proficient Software Engineer with a background in editorial and music copywriting. I have a creative mindset, and a targets-driven outlook. I am adaptable and diligent with first class communication skills developed through multiple internships spanning the music, creative, and fashion industries. My programming style is imbued with these invaluable traits.

EDUCATION

General Assembly Mar. 2019 - June 2019

Certificate for Software Engineering Immersive

King's College London Sept. 2013 - July 2017

BA Religion, Philosophy, and Ethics 2017

EMPLOYMENT

General Assembly. Software Engineering Immersive

Mar. 2019 - June 2019

During my time at General Assembly I created and developed an Event Listing application, leveraging React-on-Rails with full CRUD functionality. I worked extensively on the back-end of a project called 'Recyclo', an application which lists recycling centres within New York City, using Express and Sequelize. I also created a New York City interactive data map which leveraged React, and a Connect Four game using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS

It's Nice That, Freelance Talent Scout

Sept. 2018 - Nov. 2018

- Engaged in trend research and copywriting for a major, high-profile sportswear client.
- Worked to extremely tight deadlines, and liaised continuously with clients.

Good Machine, PR Assistant

July 2018 - Oct. 2018

- Engaged in copywriting, archived, and pitched to publications.
- Conducted and transcribed interviews.
- Created and compiled press-packs for clients.

Lucid Online. PR Intern

Mar. 2018 - Apr. 2018

- Wrote press releases for artists on the company's roster.
- Coordinated research into target audiences for up-and-coming artists.
- Successfully pitched features to a range of publications.

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT: JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Sequelize, Express, Ruby, Rails

PUBLIC RELATIONS: Copywriting, Transcription